Circular link, at least we have seen before that singly linked list and the note inside are linked
together with one single point, and we have learned about the double link at list and we have said
that they are they have two pointers that referred to the previous and next.
In Circular Link, at least, there is a much more things that are different from single living hit
list and doubling of the list in singularly linked list.
The last note refers to null, while in double or circular linked list.
This is the list, and the last one refers to the end points, though that first one.
So.
Despite that knowledge that it is referred to the last node as single link blessed the circular link,
at least by the last node inside it points to the first one.
OK, so it forms as a circle.
OK, this is that trick behind and this is what is circular.
Think less how to create a circular link at.
This is the list.
This is the nodes and they are circle linked together.
OK.
How to form this shape?
Health form this linkage.
We start by creating a structured note.
This is the note that we have created in singly linked list, contains the data and contains a pointer
to that next note.
OK, now I will create three notes had middle and last and these are two presented in the diagram above.
I will allocate the memory by using malloc memory allocation for the size of the struct, note and middle.
And last so I have created the three nodes here above in the addresses in the memory.
OK, now how to add data inside the linked list nodes the same way in sync circular and singular linked
list or singly linked list the same way in order to assign the data for the head, we put had flashed
data equal to 100.
It is the same as Java had the data method.
The data of the model equal to 200 and the data of the last is equal to three hundred.
Now, the trick behind creating a circular and the singular, the singly linked list is by referring
and making the linkage the same way had next it got to the middle middle.
And referred to the next of it is equal to the last, they are common here with a single injured list,
but that the thing that differ from the singling and this that the circular link at least.
The last note refers to the head, while in singly linked list refers last.
That next is equal to none.
This is the trick behind the circular link and list.